(Penny:)Maybe if you're working on a tuna boat.
- Hello, Penny.
- Sheldon, here is your money.
(Penny:)Thank you very much, it helped a lot.
(Sheldon:)Sarcasm?
(Sheldon:)- No.
- Darn.
(Sheldon:)I can't seem to get the hang of that.
(Leonard:)Hey, I know it's none of my business,
but where did the money come from?
(Penny:)Well, I cut back my expenses
like you said...
...and picked up more hours
at the restaurant.
(Penny:)The biggest thing was, out of the blue,
Kurt shows up...
(Penny:)...and gives me the money he owes me.
[PENNY CHUCKLES]
(Penny:)Really?
(Leonard:)Did he say why?
(Penny:)Yes. He said he was feeling guilty
and wanted to do what was right.
[PENNY CHUCKLES]
(Leonard:)That's it?
(Leonard:)Did he give any reason
as to why he came to this moral epiphany?
(Penny:)Nope. I just think he's really changed.
(Penny:)We're having dinner tomorrow night.
And I get to wear my new beret. Ha, ha.